

Dmytro Tkach

phone: +38 (066) 945-36-05 **email**: d.castidad@gmail.com

skype: tdimav353

<u>linkedIn</u>

Dmytro Tkach

WEB developer

_

Summary of Qualifications

I am a Web-programmer with more than 8+ years of work experience as PHP developer. I have work experience with Bitrix CRM/CMS (also worked with Laravel, WordPress, Joomla, HostCMS, SugarCRM, YII framework, Magento).

I am a determined and self-motivated person. Also I am a collaborative team player with communication skills. My aim is to deliver high-quality work that meets my clients' needs and exceeds their expectations.

Overall, my goal as a developer is to use my skills and knowledge to develop exceptional eCommerce websites that help businesses achieve their goals. I am constantly learning and improving to provide the best possible solutions for my clients.

Experience

<u>Столичная Ювелирная Фабрика™</u> / Web developer

March 2020 - Present

- Creating components
- Creating modules
- installation external modules
- Adding Yandex metrics and Google metrics
- Integration (with Bitrix) of HTML pages
- Website architecture development
- Improving performance of HTML pages rendering
- Creating e-mail letters
- Collaborating with other team members

AlterEGO Digital Agency / Web developer

March 2016 - March 2020

- Creating components
- Creating modules
- installation external modules
- Adding Yandex metrics and Google metrics
- Integration (with Bitrix) of HTML pages
- Website architecture development
- Improving performance of HTML pages rendering
- Creating e-mail letters
- Collaborating with other team members

Education

I've graduated as Computer Systems and Networks, Chernivtsi Industrial College, 2008 - 2012.

I've graduated as a Physical, Technical and Computer Sciences Institute of Yuriy Fedcovich Chernivtsi National University, 2012 – 2015.

Technical Skills

- PHP, JavaScript (ES5, ES6)
- HTML5, CSS 2.1, CSS Level 3
- Basic email markup, adaptive email templates, the markup for offline clients
- jQueryю, Vue, React, Angular, Backbone

- Laravel, YII framework, Symfony, Bitrix CRM/CMS, SugarCRM, Magento, WordPress, Joomla, HostCMS
- Apache, Nginx
- MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB
- Composer, Webpack, Gulp
- GIT
- JSON, XML, CSV, AJAX, RESTful-Api